{
  "Questions": [
    {
      "Question": "What year is it?",
      "Answer": "2018",
      "IncorrectAnswers": [
        "2000",
        "1992",
        "5"
      ]
    },
	{
      "Question": "What is Beebo the God of",
      "Answer": "God of War",
      "IncorrectAnswers": [
        "God of Mischief",
        "God of Thunder",
        "God of Chaos"
      ]
    },
	{
      "Question": "What is name of the CCPD Captain",
      "Answer": "David Singh",
      "IncorrectAnswers": [
        "Joe West",
        "Julian Albert",
        "Sam Scudder"
      ]
    },
	{
      "Question": "Which Earth is Accelerated Man on",
      "Answer": "Earth-19",
      "IncorrectAnswers": [
        "Earth-17",
        "Earth-39",
        "Earth-24"
      ]
    },
	{
      "Question": "When did the first episode of The Flash air",
      "Answer": "October 7, 2014",
      "IncorrectAnswers": [
        "October 9, 2014",
        "October 7, 2015",
        "October 4, 2014"
      ]
    },
	{
      "Question": "In which episode did Barry first time travel",
      "Answer": "\"Out of Time\"",
      "IncorrectAnswers": [
        "\"Fast Enough\"",
        "\"Flash Back\"",
        "\"Legends of Today\""
      ]
    },
	{
      "Question": "Which character does Teddy Sears play in The Flash",
      "Answer": "Hunter Zolomon",
      "IncorrectAnswers": [
        "Jay Garrick",
        "Black Flash",
        "Firestorm"
      ]
    },
	{
      "Question": "Who is the time travelling protagonist from the future in Legends of Tomorrow",
      "Answer": "Rip Hunter",
      "IncorrectAnswers": [
        "Marty McFly",
        "Phillip J Fry",
        "Vandal Savage"
      ]
    },
	{
      "Question": "What is the date of the newspaper inside of the Time Vault",
      "Answer": "Thursday April 25 2024",
      "IncorrectAnswers": [
        "Thursday May 24 2025",
        "Tuesday April 25 2026",
        "Tuesday April 23 2024"
      ]
    },
	{
      "Question": "How many Totems of Zambesi exist",
      "Answer": "6",
      "IncorrectAnswers": [
        "4",
        "5",
        "8"
      ]
    },
	{
      "Question": "Which character in the Arrowverse was first to be 100% CGI",
      "Answer": "Invunche",
      "IncorrectAnswers": [
        "Parasite",
        "Gorilla Grodd",
        "King Shark"
      ]
    },
	{
      "Question": "What is the time travelling organisation Rip Hunter founded in Legends of Tomorrow",
      "Answer": "Time Bureau",
      "IncorrectAnswers": [
        "Time Travellers",
        "Time Masters",
        "The Legends"
      ]
    },
	{
      "Question": "How many times has Mark Hamill appeared on the Flash as The Trickster",
      "Answer": "3",
      "IncorrectAnswers": [
        "4",
        "1",
        "2"
      ]
    },
	{
      "Question": "How many Actors/Actresses who were on The Flash (1990) have appeared on The Flash (2014)",
      "Answer": "4",
      "IncorrectAnswers": [
        "0",
        "2",
        "6"
      ]
    },
	{
      "Question": "Which actor/actress has played the most characters",
      "Answer": "Tom Cavanagh",
      "IncorrectAnswers": [
        "Grant Gustin",
        "Katie Cassidy",
        "Teddy Sears"
      ]
    },
	{
      "Question": "Which character is Jewish",
      "Answer": "Felicity Smoak",
      "IncorrectAnswers": [
        "John Constantine",
        "Kara Danvers",
        "Ray Palmer"
      ]
    },
	{
      "Question": "Which company does Arrow's Visual Effects",
      "Answer": "Zoic Studios",
      "IncorrectAnswers": [
        "Encore VFX",
        "Luma Pictures",
        "Industrial Light and Magic"
      ]
    },
	{
      "Question": "Which episode did we see Barry run the fastest",
      "Answer": "\"Enter Flashtime\"",
      "IncorrectAnswers": [
        "\"Fast Enough\"",
        "\"Enter Zoom\"",
        "\"Wrath of Savitar\""
      ]
    },
	{
      "Question": "Who made a guest appearance at the end of the Flash Season 1 finale",
      "Answer": "Kendra Saunders",
      "IncorrectAnswers": [
        "Zoom",
        "Jay Garrick",
        "Captain Cold"
      ]
    },
	{
      "Question": "How many bus metas are there in The Flash season 4",
      "Answer": "12",
      "IncorrectAnswers": [
        "6",
        "9",
        "14"
      ]
    },
	{
      "Question": "What is the enchancement drug from Arrow season 2 called",
      "Answer": "Mirakuru",
      "IncorrectAnswers": [
        "Vertigo",
        "Drug X",
        "Velocity-9"
      ]
    },
	{
      "Question": "When does Stephen Amell's Arrow contract end",
      "Answer": "2019",
      "IncorrectAnswers": [
        "2021",
        "2020",
        "2018"
      ]
    },
	{
      "Question": "Who has not travelled through time",
      "Answer": "Oliver",
      "IncorrectAnswers": [
        "Felicity",
        "Constantine",
        "Cisco"
      ]
    },
	{
      "Question": "Which Earth is The Ray, as featured in the crossover, from",
      "Answer": "Earth-1",
      "IncorrectAnswers": [
        "Earth-2",
        "Earth-X",
        "Earth-10"
      ]
    },
	{
      "Question": "How many animated shows from CW Seed are set in the Arrowverse",
      "Answer": "2",
      "IncorrectAnswers": [
        "1",
        "3",
        "4"
      ]
    },
	{
      "Question": "What Network was Supergirl on during Season 1",
      "Answer": "CBS",
      "IncorrectAnswers": [
        "The CW",
        "NBC",
        "Fox"
      ]
    },
	{
      "Question": "How many TV shows set in the Arrowverse",
      "Answer": "5",
      "IncorrectAnswers": [
        "3",
        "4",
        "6"
      ]
    },
	{
      "Question": "How many Earths in the multiverse",
      "Answer": "53",
      "IncorrectAnswers": [
        "52",
        "51",
        "Infinite"
      ]
    },
	{
      "Question": "Which of these characters don't have their own game",
      "Answer": "Green Arrow",
      "IncorrectAnswers": [
        "Constantine",
        "Superman",
        "The Flash"
      ]
    },
	{
      "Question": "What is the name of Barry's pet Turtle",
      "Answer": "McSnurtle",
      "IncorrectAnswers": [
        "Turtle",
        "Bart",
        "Cosmos"
      ]
    },
	{
      "Question": "Who played Sara Lance in the pilot episode of Arrow",
      "Answer": "Jacqueline Macinnes Wood",
      "IncorrectAnswers": [
        "Caity Lotz",
        "Kathleen Gati",
        "Wendy Mericle"
      ]
    },
	{
      "Question": "Who is the showrunner for Supergirl",
      "Answer": "Alison Adler",
      "IncorrectAnswers": [
        "Wendy Mericle",
        "Beth Schwartz",
        "Andrew Kreisberg"
      ]
    },
	{
      "Question": "Who directed the Arrow and The Flash pilot",
      "Answer": "David Nutter",
      "IncorrectAnswers": [
        "Greg Berlanti",
        "JJ Abrams",
        "Andrew Kreisberg"
      ]
    },
	{
      "Question": "Who voices Prometheus in Arrow",
      "Answer": "Michael Dorn",
      "IncorrectAnswers": [
        "Josh Segerra",
        "John Barrowman",
        "Tony Todd"
      ]
    },
	{
      "Question": "How many episodes in Legends of Tomorrow Season 2",
      "Answer": "17",
      "IncorrectAnswers": [
        "16",
        "22",
        "23"
      ]
    },
	{
      "Question": "How many episodes of Supergirl, has Superman appeared in",
      "Answer": "4",
      "IncorrectAnswers": [
        "2",
        "3",
        "1"
      ]
    },
	{
      "Question": "How long roughly was M'rnn J'onzz held imprisoned on Mars for",
      "Answer": "Centuries",
      "IncorrectAnswers": [
        "Decades",
        "Months",
        "Milleniums"
      ]
    },
	{
      "Question": "How far into the future was Mon-El sent to",
      "Answer": "1000 years",
      "IncorrectAnswers": [
        "900 years",
        "600 years",
        "500 years"
      ]
    },
	{
      "Question": "How long was the Legion's ship stuck underneath National City for",
      "Answer": "12000 years",
      "IncorrectAnswers": [
        "8000 years",
        "10000 years",
        "5000 years"
      ]
    },
	{
      "Question": "Which of the World Destroyers would go on to become Blight",
      "Answer": "Pestilence",
      "IncorrectAnswers": [
        "Reign",
        "Purity",
        "All of the above?"
      ]
    },
	{
      "Question": "How many children did J'onn J'onnzs have",
      "Answer": "2",
      "IncorrectAnswers": [
        "1",
        "3",
        "4"
      ]
    },
	{
      "Question": "What does D.E.O stand for",
      "Answer": "Department of Extra-Normal Operations",
      "IncorrectAnswers": [
        "Department of Extra Ordinaries",
        "Department of Extra-Natrual Operations",
        "Department of Extraordinary Operations"
      ]
    },
	{
      "Question": "How many currently known members are part of the Legion of Superheroes",
      "Answer": "7",
      "IncorrectAnswers": [
        "2",
        "3",
        "6"
      ]
    },
    {
      "Question": "Who plays Vandal Savage",
      "Answer": "Casper Crump",
      "IncorrectAnswers": [
        "Falk Hentschel",
        "Glen Winter",
        "Neal McDonough"
      ]
    }
  ]
}